

## Behnam Khoshsafar

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - JAVA

#### **PROFILE**

Nationality: Iranian
Birth Date: 09/06/1990

A passionate and hard-working developer with experience in designing and developing software in Java since 2014.

Participated in implementing different types of applications specializing in backend development. Skilled in Spring, JPA, and Object Oriented Design.

#### **EDUCATION**

Master of Science from Qom University in Information technology - E-commerce from September 2012 to February 2015.

Bachelor of Science from Kurdestan University in Information technology from September 2008 to September 2012.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English

Persian

#### **CONTACT**

Email: b.khoshsafar@gmail.com

Mobile: +98 937 375 1121

LinkedIn: Khoshsafar's profile

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### MyDigipay

#### Senior Java Developer

Mar 2019 - Present

- Working as a member of the Credit team.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Installment module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Refund module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Report module.

#### Sava Arman Kish (Bitex)

#### Senior Java Developer

July 2018 - Mar 2019

- Worked as a member of the development team.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Order module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Notification module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Report module.

#### Navaco (Maskan Bank)

#### Java Developer

Feb 2017 - July 2018

- Worked as a member of the Lending team.
- Designed and implemented lending overnight calculation.
- Designed and implemented the Letter of Credit subsystem

#### Hamgam Corporate Group

#### Java Developer

April 2014 - Jan 2017

- Worked as a member of the development team.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Sale module.
- Responsible for designing and implementing the Inventory module.



# Behnam Khoshsafar

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - JAVA

### PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Java	Spring
Groovy	Spring Boot
Design Patterns	Spring MVC
Microservices	Spring Batch
Test Driven Development	Spring Security
Concurrent Programming	Spring Cloud Config
RESTful Web Services	Spring Cloud Netflix
Swagger	Spring Cloud Gateway
JUnit / Mockito / WireMock	Spring Cloud Sleuth
Oracle	Spring Cloud Zipkin
MySQL	Spring Data / JPA
MongoDB	Spring WebFlux
Redis	Reactive Programming
Hibernate	Eureka / Ribbon / Hystrix / Zuul Netflix
Docker and Docker Compose	Git / Subversion
CI / CD	UML / Agile and RUP Methodologies
RabbitMQ	Lending System Developer
Maven / Gradle	CORE Banking Systems
Exchange Developing	